<?xml version="1.0" ?>
    <rss version="2.0"  xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
        <channel>
            <title>RSS feed for tag axpbox on Raymii.org</title> 
            <link>https://raymii.org/s/tags/axpbox.xml</link> 
            <description>RSS feed for tag axpbox on Raymii.org</description>
            <atom:link href="https://raymii.org/s/tags/axpbox.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
            <item>
                <title>Installing OpenVMS 8.4 Alpha inside AXPbox on Debian 10 / Ubuntu 20.04 with networking</title> 
                <link>https://raymii.org/s/tutorials/Installing_OpenVMS_8.4_Alpha_in_AXPbox_with_networking.html</link> 
                <guid>https://raymii.org/s/tutorials/Installing_OpenVMS_8.4_Alpha_in_AXPbox_with_networking.html</guid>
                <description>In my previous article I announced the fork of the `es40` emulator to `AXPbox` by Tom&amp;aacute;&amp;scaron; including bug fixes and rework allowing it to install OpenVMS 8.4 without problems. Since then I've contributed a few patches and doc updates, now NetBSD boots as well (the patches for netbsd were from other es40 forks). I've also looked into getting networking setup, since that is a bit of a tedious process due to pcap and linux, pcap being used for network emulation. SIMH (among others, a great VAX emulator) suffers from the same problems with networking. This guide will show you how to install AXPbox and get OpenVMS 8.4 ready and running with networking inside AXPbox. It's a rather long guide with a lot of information and output.</description> 
                <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2020 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
            </item>
    
            <item>
                <title>Exciting OpenVMS Alpha Emulation news, es40 has been forked to Axpbox (and works!)</title> 
                <link>https://raymii.org/s/blog/Exciting_OpenVMS_Alpha_emulation_news_es40_has_been_forked_to_axpbox.html</link> 
                <guid>https://raymii.org/s/blog/Exciting_OpenVMS_Alpha_emulation_news_es40_has_been_forked_to_axpbox.html</guid>
                <description>Back in 2018 I was playing around with OpenVMS a lot, as it continues on the legacy of the PDP-8 and PDP-11. OpenVMS 7.3 on the VAX emulated via SIMH runs perfectly, OpenVMS 8.4 for Alpha was kind of a disaster, or, the es40 emulator was. Real hardware is available via IslandCo, but shipping to the Netherlands is horribly expensive.
The only options back then for emulation of Alpha were FreeAXP or AlphaVM, both paid, closed sourced products with watered down free versions. Nothing wrong with that, it enables us to play around, and now that OpenVMS is in the hands of VMS Software with an x86 port coming along we may hope for a bright future ahead for OpenVMS. VSI currently provides a hobbyist version, but it's a FreeAXP bundle for Windows only.
Recently I got an email from Tom&amp;aacute;&amp;scaron; regarding his fork of the es40 emulator, axpbox. This short post is intended to give this emulator more visibility and exposure, since I find this to be amazingly cool and exciting. It lists the bugs fixed and new features, which allow OpenVMS 8.3 and 8.4 to install perfectly.</description> 
                <pubDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                <lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Oct 2020 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
            </item>
    
        </channel>
    </rss>
    
    