<?xml version="1.0" ?>
    <rss version="2.0"  xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
        <channel>
            <title>RSS feed for tag development on Raymii.org</title> 
            <link>https://raymii.org/s/tags/development.xml</link> 
            <description>RSS feed for tag development on Raymii.org</description>
            <atom:link href="https://raymii.org/s/tags/development.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
            <item>
                <title>C++ variadic template recursive example</title> 
                <link>https://raymii.org/s/snippets/Cpp_variadic_template_recursive_example.html</link> 
                <guid>https://raymii.org/s/snippets/Cpp_variadic_template_recursive_example.html</guid>
                <description>In this article I'll show you how to use a variadic template in C++. Variadic templates allow you to have a template with a variable number of arguments, also called a parameter pack. Unpacking that pack is more difficult than it should be, so we use a recursive template to iterate over all the parameters one by one. I've also included an example in Python to compare to.</description> 
                <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2019 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                <lastBuildDate>Sat, 08 Jun 2019 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
            </item>
    
            <item>
                <title>C++ create and write to a CSV file</title> 
                <link>https://raymii.org/s/snippets/Cpp_create_and_write_to_a_csv_file.html</link> 
                <guid>https://raymii.org/s/snippets/Cpp_create_and_write_to_a_csv_file.html</guid>
                <description>In this quick snippet I'll show you how to create and write to a csv file. It includes checking if the file is writable, and if it's not there, creates it with a different first row as header. It's a quick example, I've used it to log some test data. It can probably be improved.</description> 
                <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                <lastBuildDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2019 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
            </item>
    
            <item>
                <title>Shared Git repository over ssh for multiple users</title> 
                <link>https://raymii.org/s/tutorials/Shared_Git_repository_via_ssh_for_multiple_users.html</link> 
                <guid>https://raymii.org/s/tutorials/Shared_Git_repository_via_ssh_for_multiple_users.html</guid>
                <description>This tutorial will show you how to set up a shared git repo with multiple accounts over ssh. Only ssh, not gitolite or any other software. This is usefull if you have a small team of people that don't often need access to the repo and don't want something like github or bitbucket. With this you can use existing infrastructure.</description> 
                <pubDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2015 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                <lastBuildDate>Mon, 05 Jan 2015 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
            </item>
    
        </channel>
    </rss>
    
    