<?xml version="1.0" ?>
    <rss version="2.0"  xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
        <channel>
            <title>RSS feed for tag dpkg on Raymii.org</title> 
            <link>https://raymii.org/s/tags/dpkg.xml</link> 
            <description>RSS feed for tag dpkg on Raymii.org</description>
            <atom:link href="https://raymii.org/s/tags/dpkg.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
            <item>
                <title>I've packaged up Gnash as a snap, for modern linux</title> 
                <link>https://raymii.org/s/blog/Ive_packaged_up_Gnash_as_a_Snap_for_modern_linux.html</link> 
                <guid>https://raymii.org/s/blog/Ive_packaged_up_Gnash_as_a_Snap_for_modern_linux.html</guid>
                <description>I hate snaps just as much as the next guy but last week I did something unexpected. I packaged up Gnash as a snap.  Gnash is a GNU flash media player, not updated since 2011, and  thus removed from the Ubuntu 20.04 repositories. The snap packaging is based on work by phil roche, he wrote about re-packaging older debian packages with an Ubuntu 18.04/16.04 base layer as a snap. My gnash package is confined (no '--classic' needed), the source code for the snap is on my github and on any snap-enabled distro you can now 'snap install gnash-raymii' to enjoy Gnash again.</description> 
                <pubDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                <lastBuildDate>Mon, 07 Dec 2020 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
            </item>
    
            <item>
                <title>Running gnash on Ubuntu 20.04 (in Docker with X11 forwarding)</title> 
                <link>https://raymii.org/s/tutorials/Running_gnash_on_Ubuntu_20.04.html</link> 
                <guid>https://raymii.org/s/tutorials/Running_gnash_on_Ubuntu_20.04.html</guid>
                <description>As you might have noticed, I'm slowly updating servers and workstations to Ubuntu 20.04, and as always with major upgrades, things break or are removed. Earlier this week I fixed up pygopherd and today I'll get gnash running again. Gnash is not updated since 2011 and therefore, finally, removed from the Ubuntu 20.04 repositories. Compiling it from source proved to be a lot of effort due to gstreamer dependencies and after a few hours I thought, why not just spin up a Ubuntu 18.04 Docker container, install gnash and forward X11. That took just about 10 minutes and now I'm happily running gnash again. In this tutorial I'll show you how to setup gnash in a docker container with x11 forwarding and host networking.</description> 
                <pubDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Jul 2020 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
            </item>
    
            <item>
                <title>Installing PyGopherd on Ubuntu 20.04</title> 
                <link>https://raymii.org/s/tutorials/Installing_PyGopherd_on_Ubuntu_20.04.html</link> 
                <guid>https://raymii.org/s/tutorials/Installing_PyGopherd_on_Ubuntu_20.04.html</guid>
                <description>Ubuntu 20.04 dropped the Pygopherd package. There is no way to install it from the official repositories. In this guide I'll show you two ways to install the version from Ubuntu 18.04, which still works perfectly on 20.04. Either via just downloading the 2 deb packages, or via `apt pinning` from the previous (18.04) repository.</description> 
                <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2020 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2020 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
            </item>
    
            <item>
                <title>Silent unatended apt-get upgrade</title> 
                <link>https://raymii.org/s/tutorials/Silent-automatic-apt-get-upgrade.html</link> 
                <guid>https://raymii.org/s/tutorials/Silent-automatic-apt-get-upgrade.html</guid>
                <description>This tutorial will show you how to setup completely silent apt-get upgrade via cron. It also defaults to not overwriting config files if a package has a newer version.</description> 
                <pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2013 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                <lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2013 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
            </item>
    
            <item>
                <title>Packages</title> 
                <link>https://raymii.org/s/software/Software_packages.html</link> 
                <guid>https://raymii.org/s/software/Software_packages.html</guid>
                <description>Some software I encounter does not have a debian .deb package available. Via the ./configure, make, sudo checkinstall I compile them into a package and put it up here for download.</description> 
                <pubDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2012 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Sep 2012 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
            </item>
    
            <item>
                <title>Debian packages clean up commands</title> 
                <link>https://raymii.org/s/tutorials/Debian-apt-get-dpkg-packages-cleanup-commands.html</link> 
                <guid>https://raymii.org/s/tutorials/Debian-apt-get-dpkg-packages-cleanup-commands.html</guid>
                <description>Not available.</description> 
                <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2010 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
                <lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Jan 2010 00:00:00 GMT</lastBuildDate>
            </item>
    
        </channel>
    </rss>
    
    